I'M GETTING COFFEE TO GO.
BABY DOLL?
I'M FINE. THANKS.
YEAH, SEE, I CAN'T PULL OFF
"BABY DOLL," CAN I?
NO. I THINK WE LEARNED THAT FROM
THE "SUGAR LIPS" INCIDENT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SOME TEA.
HOW YOU DOING, PUNKIN'?
NOPE.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GOING REALLY WELL
FOR YOU TWO, HUH?
REALLY WELL. IN FACT...
I'M GOING TO ASK PHOEBE
TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THAT IS SO GREAT.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO ASK HER?
TONIGHT,
BUT DON'T SAY ANYTHING, OKAY?
I SWEAR. I PROMISE,
I PROMISE.
MY GOD, I'M SO EXCITED.
ALL RIGHT, BUT LISTEN,
LET ME TELL YOU:
DO NOT GET HER
FLOWERS, OKAY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
SHE CRIES WHEN THEY DIE
AND THEN THERE'S
THE WHOLE FUNERAL...
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER WORK,
SWEETIE.
OKAY. BYE.
SO, WHAT MOVIE
SHOULD WE SEE?
GARY'S GOING TO ASK YOU
TO MOVE IN WITH HIM!
WHAT? REALLY?
HE JUST TOLD ME
AT THE COUNTER.
HE MADE ME PROMISE
NOT TO TELL
BUT I COULDN'T HOLD
IT ANY LONGER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
RIGHT, BUT BECAUSE
IT'S FAST.
BECAUSE IT'S SO FAST.
RELAX. IT'S PHOEBE,
NOT YOU.
OH. GOOD FOR YOU, PHEEBS.
WAY TO GO.
BUT IT IS FAST,
ISN'T IT?
OH...
I LIKE HIM A LOT,
BUT I'M NOT READY.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL JUST HANDLE IT.
I'LL ASK YOU TO TALK TO HIM.
ME? WHY ME?
BECAUSE YOU ARE SO AFRAID
OF COMMITMENT.
YOU TALK TO HIM.
MAKE HIM SCARED LIKE YOU.
MAKE HIM A-A MAN.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'LL TRY
BUT I'M NOT SURE WHAT GOOD
IT WOULD DO, YOU KNOW
BECAUSE I'M A LOT LESS AFRAID
OF COMMITMENT
THAN I USED TO BE.
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
STILL TERRIFIED.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
NO PROBLEM.
( chuckling )
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY, ROSS, IS, UH...
IS STATEN ISLAND
REALLY AN ISLAND?
UH-HUH.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT STATEN
ISLAND.
OH. I THOUGHT IT WAS LIKE
LONG ISLAND.
ALSO AN ISLAND.
HEY, WHAT TIME IS IT?
2:17.
WOW, YOU REALIZE
WE'VE BEEN THROWING THIS BALL
WITHOUT DROPPING IT
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I REALIZED IT A HALF HOUR AGO,
BUT DIDN'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING
'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO JINX IT.
OH.
WOW, WE ARE PRETTY GOOD AT THIS.
( chuckling ):
YEAH.
HEY... WE TOTALLY FORGOT
ABOUT LUNCH.
OH. I THINK THAT'S THE FIRST
TIME I'VE EVER MISSED A MEAL.
YEAH?
YEAH. I THINK MY PANTS
ARE A LITTLE LOOSE.
HEY, YOU GUYS, UH...
IS MONICA HERE?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN
I JUST BOUGHT SOMETHING.
I'M NOT SURE
SHE'S GOING TO LIKE IT
AND IT'S GOING TO SEEM
A LITTLE CRAZY
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING
I'VE WANTED
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
YOU BOUGHT SHAUN CASSIDY!
NO. I WISH.
OKAY... YOU READY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
CHECK IT OUT.
OH, MY GOD! WHAT-WHAT IS...
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
IT'S-IT'S A CAT.
THAT IS NOT A CAT.
YES, IT IS.
WHY IS IT INSIDE OUT?
EXCUSE ME
BUT THIS IS A PUREBRED,
SHOW-QUALITY SPHINX CAT.
HOW MUCH DID YOU
PAY FOR THAT?
IT WAS EXTRAVAGANT,
BUT I GOT A PRETTY GOOD DEAL.
YEAH? HOW MUCH?
A THOUSAND BUCKS.
ON A CAT?!
IT'S NOT A CAT.
WHAT...?
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, BALL BOYS
MY GRANDMOTHER HAD ONE OF THESE
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL
AND IT WAS THE SWEETEST THING.
I MEAN, IT WAS SO CUTE.
IT WOULD SIT IN MY LAP
AND JUST PURR ALL DAY LONG
AND I WOULD DRAG A SHOESTRING
ON THE GROUND
AND IT WOULD CHASE IT.
FREE CATS DO THAT,
TOO, YOU KNOW.
IT'S NOT A CAT!
LOOK, YOU GUYS, I'M REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU THINK.
I'M GOING TO GO SET UP A
LITTER BOX FOR MRS. WHISKERSON.
WELL, WHAT AM I GOING
TO CALL HER-- FLUFFY?
YOU WANT TO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT
OR TO SEE HOW LONG
WE CAN THROW THIS BALL
BACK AND FORTH, HUH?
UH... THE BALL THING.
YEAH?
HEY, ROSS,
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF WE COULD GO FOR, LIKE,
TWO STRAIGHT HOURS
WITHOUT DROPPING IT?
UH... YEAH, IT WOULD.
LET'S DO IT.
OKAY.
UH-OH.
WHAT?
I HAVE TO PEE
AND RACHEL'S IN THE BATHROOM.
MAN, I DIDN'T THINK
WE WERE GOING TO MAKE IT.
I KNOW.
DON'T SWITCH HANDS, OKAY?
HEY, LADIES, WHAT ARE
YOU IN HERE FOR?
( laughs )
HEY, CHANDLER,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
GARY, I AM HERE
TO REPORT A CRIME.
YEAH?
IT IS A CRIME WE DON'T
SPEND MORE TIME TOGETHER.
( mock chuckle ):
WHAT'S UP?
UH, WELL, I HEARD
THAT YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT
ASKING PHOEBE
TO MOVE IN WITH YOU
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE SHOULD HAVE A TALK
YOU KNOW, MAN-TO... WELL, ME.
SURE. OKAY.
OKAY.
UM, ARE YOU CRAZY?
ARE YOU INSANE?
IF YOU LIVE WITH PHOEBE
YOU TWO ARE GOING TO BE
YOU KNOW, L-LIVING TOGETHER.
YEAH. I CONSIDERED THAT.
I JUST KNOW
IT'D MAKE ME HAPPY.
( laughs ):
YOU MEAN SCARED.
NO, I MEAN HAPPY.
WELL, "SCARED HAPPY."
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM TRYING TO OPEN YOUR EYES,
MY MAN.
DON'T YOU SEE?
IF YOU LIVE WITH PHOEBE
SHE'S ALWAYS GOING
TO BE THERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
HOME-- SHE'S THERE.
YOU GO TO BED--
SHE'S THERE.
YOU WAKE UP, AND,
OH, YES-- SHE'S THERE.
I KNOW. I CAN'T WAIT.
WERE YOUR PARENTS
HAPPY OR SOMETHING?
LISTEN, CHANDLER,
THE WAY I SEE IT IS
I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH TO FIND
SOMEONE I REALLY LOVE.
I JUST... I WANT TO BE AROUND
HER AS MUCH AS I CAN.
WOW, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU SAY IT
IT DOESN'T SOUND SO SCARY.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YEAH, I THINK I DO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU MOVE IN WITH HER.
YOU MOVE IN
WITH HER RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE I SHOULD MOVE
IN WITH MONICA.
NO, IT'S TOO SOON FOR YOU GUYS.
( chuckling ):
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
NOW, WHEN THEY
FOUND THE REMAINS
OF THE MESOZOIC MASTODON
THEY DISCOVERED
WHAT APPEARED TO BE
THE REMAINS OF A PALEOZOIC
AMPHIBIAN IN ITS JAWS.
HOW DID IT GET THERE?
MAYBE THIS SHOULD BE
MORE OF A QUIET GAME.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
I LEFT MY WATCH
ON THE COUNTER LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS RIGHT HERE.
WHERE IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, COME ON.
I'M LATE FOR WORK.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
YOU DON'T HAVE A WATCH.
GUYS, COULD YOU PLEASE JUST STOP
THROWING THE BALL FOR ONE MINUTE
AND JUST HELP ME FIND IT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, CAN'T DO IT.
NO! D...
AAH! AAH!
WHAT?
MONICA, WHATEVER YOU DO,
DO NOT DROP THAT BALL.
YEAH. WE HAVEN'T
DROPPED IT IN...
TWO HOURS,
27 MINUTES.
REALLY?
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT INTO WORK TODAY.
( congested voice ):
UM, I DON'T FEEL VERY GOOD.
YES!
WOW, UH, FOR A SECOND THERE
I THOUGHT I WAS FEELING BETTER,
BUT I'M NOT.
BYE.
Ross:
HEY, RACH.
HEY.
CHECK IT OUT--
ALMOST THREE HOURS
WITHOUT DROPPING IT.
WHOO.
OH, WOW. CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S QUITE A WASTE OF TIME.
RACH?
YEAH?
YOU HAVE SCRATCHES ALL OVER.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, IT'S MY CAT.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH. I GOT A CAT.
I DON'T WANT A CAT.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
IT'S NOT A CAT.
YEAH.
YOU GUYS
THIS CAT IS NOTHING LIKE
MY GRANDMOTHER'S CAT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT SWEET;
IT'S NOT CUTE.
I EVEN DRAGGED THAT
LITTLE STRING ON THE GROUND
AND IT J-JUST FLIPPED OUT AND
SCRATCHED THE HELL OUT OF ME...
AND I SWEAR--
I KNOW THIS SOUNDS CRAZY--
BUT EVERY TIME
THIS CAT HISSES AT ME
I KNOW IT'S SAYING:
( whispering ):
"RACHEL."
DOESN'T SOUND AS CRAZY
AS PAYING $1,000 FOR A CAT.
WHA...! YOU PAID
$1,000 FOR A CAT
WHEN YOU OWE ME $300?
WELL, I... I WAS GOING TO LET
YOU PLAY WITH IT.
HEY.
MM... DID YOU TALK
TO GARY
ABOUT THE MOVING IN THING?
YES, I DID, AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD DO IT.
WHAT?
HE'S A GREAT GUY, YOU KNOW,
AND HE LOVES YOU A LOT.
YOU ARE A VERY LUCKY LADY.
YOU ARE USELESS.
FREAKING OUT ABOUT COMMITMENT
IS THE ONE THING YOU CAN DO--
THE ONE THING-- AND YOU
CAN'T EVEN DO THAT RIGHT.
GOD.
I'M SORRY.
IF HE ASKED ME,
I'D MOVE IN WITH HIM.
OH!
GOD.
OOH, GET OUT OF HERE,
YOU GOOD-FOR-NOTHING.
HEY, CHANDLER.
HEY, GAR.
HEY, SWEETIE.
HI. CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A SECOND?
YEAH... 'KAY.
YOU LOOK VERY PRETTY TODAY.
THANKS. OKAY.
HERE'S THE THING--
YEAH?
I REALLY WANT
THIS RELATIONSHIP
TO MOVE FORWARD...
MM-HMM.
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE
NOT MOVING FORWARD
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE JUST
MOVING BACKWARDS.
NOW, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IF YOU'RE NOT MOVING FORWARD,
YOU'RE JUST STAYING STILL
AND STAYING STILL IS GOOD.
WATCH THIS.
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
I WANT YOU TO
MOVE IN WITH ME.
THAT IS SO SWEET
BUT DON'T YOU THINK THAT
IT'S A LITTLE TOO SOON?
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
THAT WE DON'T KNOW
ABOUT EACH OTHER.
OH.
OH, OKAY, I GET IT.
I JUST... I DON'T WANT US
TO JUMP INTO SOMETHING
YOU KNOW, THAT WE'RE NOT...
READY FOR.
YOU KNOW?
( trembling voice ):
UH-HUH.
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO MESS UP WHAT WE HAVE.
I'M JUST... I'M WORRIED IT'S
GOING TO BE A BIG MISTAKE.
HUH.
WHICH IS WHY MY ANSWER IS YES!
REALLY?
UH-HUH.
OH, YOU'RE SO HAPPY.
MONICA, STOP THROWING IT
SO HARD!
WE'RE ON THE SAME TEAM.
FOUR HOURS?
YOU GUYS HAVE
BEEN DOING THIS
FOR FOUR HOURS?
THAT'S RIGHT,
BABY.
ALL RIGHT, LET ME IN.
NO, NO! DON'T DO IT!
DON'T!
WHAT?
HE'S A DROPPER.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
I'M NOT A DROPPER!
IT'S REALLY A-A-A...
THREE-PERSON GAME, YOU KNOW?
IT'S THROWING AND CATCHING.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, OH, IT'S SO HARD.
DON'T WORRY, GUYS.
IT'S NOT A CAT.
OH, MY...
OH, GOOD GOD.
I GIVE UP, YOU GUYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO WITH THIS THING.
BAKING IT DIDN'T HELP, HUH?
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAKE IT BACK
TO WHERE YOU GOT IT?
I TRIED.
THEY WON'T TAKE HER BACK.
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE SHE'S
A MINION OF THE ANTI-CHRIST.
RACH...
WHY WON'T THEY
TAKE IT BACK?
WELL, THEY SAID THEY WOULD
BUT THEY WOULD ONLY GIVE ME
STORE CREDIT
AND, I MEAN,
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
GET A THOUSAND REGULAR CATS?
YOU CAN KEEP IT
AT OUR PLACE
UNTIL YOU FIND OUT
WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
NO, MON, THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
I AM OUT $1,000;
I AM ALL SCRATCHED UP
AND I'M STUCK WITH THIS STUPID
CAT THAT LOOKS LIKE A HAND.
( sneezes )
OH, MY GOD.
THE CAT'S MADE
MY EYES WATER.
DON'T-DON'T
THROW IT TO ME!
MY VISION'S
BEEN COMPROMISED!
OH, GOD. OKAY, OKAY...
IT'S OKAY.
MAN, THAT WAS CLOSE.
YEAH. YOU ALMOST OVERREACTED
TO SOMETHING.
HEY.
WE HAVE GREAT NEWS.
WE'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER!
ISN'T IT GREAT? YAY!
YAY!
CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S GREAT.
I KNOW. I'M SO EXCITED.
SO AM I.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT
MORE EXCITED THAN I AM.
NO WAY.
I'M THE MOST EXCITED.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE STATION LATER.
YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
DON'T FORGET
ABOUT THE MOVING IN.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE MOVING IN WITH
HIM? WHAT HAPPENED?
I COULDN'T TELL HIM NO--
HE GOT SO SAD.
BUT MAYBE IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I DO REALLY
LIKE HIM A LOT
AND WOULD PROBABLY DO IT
EVENTUALLY ANYWAY...
AND, PLUS, THINK OF ALL
THE MONEY I'LL SAVE ON STAMPS.
WHY, DO YOU
WRITE HIM A LOT?
NO. I JUST HEARD
WHEN PEOPLE LIVE TOGETHER
THEY SPLIT THE COST OF STAMPS,
DON'T THEY?
YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT. YEAH, YEAH.
OH!
OH... I'M SORRY.
THE OVEN MITTS
REALLY FREAKED ME OUT.
HI, HONEY.
HEY, HONEY.
DID YOU FIND ANY APARTMENTS
IN BROOKLYN HEIGHTS?
NO. NOTHING.
OH. REALLY?
YEAH.
NOTHING AT ALL?
NO.
AS SOON AS SOMETHING OPENS UP,
WE'LL MOVE RIGHT IN.
UNLESS IT DOESN'T HAVE A POOL;
I NEED A POOL.
PHOEBE, CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
UH-HUH.
TAKE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU OKAY?
YOU FEELING
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I FEEL GREAT,
'CAUSE WE'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER.
SO YOU, UH...
YOU CHECKED THE PAPER
FOR LISTINGS
IN BROOKLYN
HEIGHTS, RIGHT?
YOU-YOU CHECKED THE POST?
YEAH. UH-HUH. THERE WAS NOTHING.
COULD I GET SOME WATER?
IN A MINUTE.
YOU-YOU CHECKED TODAY'S POST?
UM, YEAH. TODAY'S. MM-HMM.
HMM...
'CAUSE, UH, THIS
IS TODAY'S POST
AND, UH, THESE ARE
THE LISTINGS I FOUND.
"BROOKLYN HEIGHTS,
TWO BEDROOMS."
ONE BEDROOM."
"BROOKLYN HEIGHTS," "BROOKLYN
HEIGHTS," "BROOKLYN HEIGHTS."
OH, ARE THESE FOR RENT?
I THOUGHT PEOPLE
WERE JUST BRAGGING.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT I THINK
MIGHT BE GOING ON HERE.
NO, NO. DON'T
LOOK AT THE TABLE.
LOOK AT ME.
OKAY?
I THINK SOMEBODY ASKED SOMEONE
TO MOVE IN WITH HIM
AND I THINK SOMEONE SAID YES
BUT NOW SHE'S HAVING
DOUBTS 'CAUSE
MAYBE THINGS ARE MOVING TOO FAST
FOR SOMEONE.
DOES THAT SOUND AT ALL
POSSIBLE TO YOU?
YES, YES, YES, FINE!
I AM SOMEONE!
YOU WANT ME TO SAY IT?
I HAVE DOUBTS.
I'M SORRY!
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
PHOEBE, IT'S OKAY
THAT YOU FEEL THIS WAY.
I MEAN, IT IS SOON
AND THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS
WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT EACH OTHER.
I FIGURED EVERYTHING I KNOW
ABOUT YOU, I REALLY LIKE;
AND THE THINGS I DON'T KNOW,
I'D GET TO LEARN ABOUT
IN A PLACE WITH BOTH OUR
NAMES ON THE MAILBOX.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
SWEETHEART
BUT NONE OF THAT MATTERS
IF IT'S TOO SOON FOR YOU.
IT'S FINE. WE DON'T HAVE
TO MOVE IN TOGETHER.
I JUST... I WANT
YOU TO BE HAPPY.
LIVING WITH YOU
WOULD MAKE ME HAPPY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY THAT.
NO, I REALLY WANT
TO LIVE WITH YOU.
I WANT TO MOVE IN WITH YOU.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES. DEFINITELY, YES.
LET'S LIVE IN AN APARTMENT
THAT WE BOTH LIVE IN.
OH, THAT'S GREAT!
OH, WAIT.
ONE SEC, ONE SEC.
HEY, YOU-- BEHIND THE GLASS--
WHO ARE YOU LOOKING AT?!
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SAY THAT
EVERY TIME I WAS
IN ONE OF THESE ROOMS
WHICH WAS NEVER.
Rachel:
SHOW CAT!
QUALITY SHOW CAT!
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR BABY?
NO, THAT'S NOT A BABY.
THAT'S A CAT.
EWW, IT'S CREEPY LOOKING.
OH, NO.
ACTUALLY, IT'S VERY SWEET.
IT'S VERY SWEET. LOOK.
( vicious hissing )
YEAH. DO YOU WANT IT?
( chuckling )
NO. I HATE CATS.
WELL, SO, THEN WHAT ARE
YOU DOING TO ME? OKAY?
JUST GET OUT OF HERE,
ALL RIGHT? MOVE ON.
SHEESH.
WOW, WHAT AN UNUSUAL CAT.
YES. THANK YOU. EXACTLY.
YOU WANT IT?
MAYBE.
I WAS THINKING
ABOUT GETTING A CAT.
I WAS JUST GOING TO GO
TO THE SHELTER, BUT...
OKAY, WHY NOT?
OH, TERRIFIC.
THAT'LL BE $2,000.
WHAT?
OKAY, $1,000.
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED ME
TO ADOPT YOUR CAT.
WELL, I DO
BUT YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO ACTUALLY LOOK AT THIS
AS MORE OF AN INVESTMENT
THAN A CAT.
OKAY, YEAH.
I JUST WANTED A CAT.
YEAH. OKAY, OKAY...
( stammering )
OBVIOUSLY, YOU KNOW
HOW TO HAGGLE
SO I'M NOT GOING TO TRY
AND TAKE YOU ON, OKAY?
SO $800 AND I DON'T CALL
THE COPS, WHICH I SHOULD
BECAUSE YOU ARE
ROBBING ME BLIND! BLIND!
JUST TAKE THE CAT, LEAVE
THE MONEY AND RUN AWAY.
JUST RUN AWAY.
DAMN IT!
CAN'T YOU AT LEAST SMILE
OR SOMETHING?
( vicious hissing )
OKAY, DID ANYBODY
JUST HEAR THAT?
ANYBODY?
I'M STARVING.
COME ON, GUYS,
SUCK IT UP.
WE'RE CLOSING IN ON TEN HOURS.
IT'S GUT-CHECK TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHO MADE YOU
THE BOSS, ALL RIGHT?
WE INVENTED THIS GAME.
Monica:
PLEASE.
I MADE THIS GAME WHAT IT IS.
NOT FUN ANYMORE?
I'M STILL HUNGRY.
THERE'S PIZZA
AT MY PLACE.
WE CAN ALL EAT
WITH ONE HAND, RIGHT?
ARE YOU WITH ME?
I AM.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
COME ON! COME ON!
LET'S GO, TEAM MONICA!
WE CAN WORK OUT
THAT NAME LATER.
RACHEL...
WHAT IS YOUR CAT DOING
IN ONE OF MY BOWLS?
IT'S NOT.
I'M DEFROSTING A CHICKEN.
OH, I SOLD MRS. WHISKERSON.
OH, THANK GOD.
DID YOU GET YOUR MONEY BACK?
YEAH. $1,500.
I JUST CAME
FOR THE RED VELVET PILLOW.
OH, YEAH.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS, RACHEL,
AND, UH, DON'T FORGET
YOU CAN COME VISIT HER
ANYTIME YOU WANT.
OH, GOOD. GREAT.
I-I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
HEY.
SO WHAT IS THIS, SOME KIND
OF SNAKE OR SOMETHING?
( bird chirping )
I REALLY LIKE WAKING UP
WITH YOU.
I LIKE WAKING UP
WITH YOU, TOO.
OH, IT'S SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
I COULD STAY HERE ALL DAY.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
WE COULD HAVE
BREAKFAST IN BED...
WELL, JUST A SECOND.
OKAY.
OH!
( chirping stops )
OH, NO.
ALL RIGHT,
COME ON, MONICA!
LOOK ALIVE.
COME ON, LOOK ALIVE.
OH, GOOD, YOU'RE ALL UP.
HEY.
PHOEBE, IT'S 6:00
IN THE MORNING.
WHY AREN'T YOU
AT GARY'S?
OH, YEAH. THAT'S OVER.
WHAT?
GARY'S SUCH A GREAT GUY.
WHATEVER THE PROBLEM IS,
YOU CAN WORK IT OUT.
HE SHOT A BIRD.
OH, THAT IS OVER.
Rachel:
OH, HONEY,
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
PHOEBE, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WELL, HEY,
HERE, PHEEBS.
OH. NAH, I DON'T FEEL
LIKE PLAYING.
( collective gasp )
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, OKAY?
LOOK...
JUST PRETEND THAT
IT DIDN'T HAPPEN, OKAY?
NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW.
PHOEBE... PHOEBE'S NOT
AN OFFICIAL BALLPLAYER.
I MEAN, ONLY OFFICIAL
BALLPLAYERS CAN DROP THE BALL.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
OKAY.
Rachel:
PHOEBE, WANT TO GET
SOME BREAKFAST?
YEAH.
OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S RACE.
FIRST ONE THERE WINS.
HA-HA!
YOU GUYS WANT
TO EAT HERE?
YEAH.
OH, MAN, THAT
WAS GREAT, HUH?
CAN YOU BELIEVE HOW LONG
WE THREW THAT BALL AROUND?
I KNOW. IT IS AMAZING
IT LASTED THAT LONG.
I KNOW. MY ARM
IS KILLING ME.
NO. I MEANT WITH THE DROPPER
OVER HERE.
Ross:
OH, YEAH.
HOW DID I GET THIS REPUTATION
AS A DROPPER, OKAY?
I'M ANYTHING BUT A DROPPER.
ROSS.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]